Guide to the Acquisitions Department, Yale University Library, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records, 1946-1979; Accession 19ND-A-113
  - Acknowledgements
    - 1971-1972
      - G, 1971-1972 (Box 85, Folder 481)
      - Ha, 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 482)
      - He - Hz, 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 483)
      - I, 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 484)
      - J, 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 485)
      - K, 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 486)
      - L, 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 487)
      - Mc - Ma, 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 488)
      - Mb - Mz, 1971-1972 (Box 86, Folder 489)
      - N, 1971-1972 (Box 87, Folder 490)
      - O, 1971-1972 (Box 87, Folder 491)
      - Pa, 1971-1972 (Box 87, Folder 492)
      - Pb - Q, 1971-1972 (Box 87, Folder 493)
      - R, 1971-1972 (Box 87, Folder 494)
      - Sa - Se, 1971-1972 (Box 87, Folder 495)
      - Sh - Sz, 1971-1972 (Box 87, Folder 496)
      - T, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 497)
      - U - V, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 498)
      - Wa, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 499)
      - We - Wh, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 500)
      - Wi, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 501)
      - Wj - Z, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 502)
      - Yale, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 503)
      - Library Associates, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 504)
      - Gift Statistics and Donor Lists, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 505)
      - Appraisals, 1971-1972 (Box 88, Folder 506)
      - Card file of Yale publications received by Yale University Library, Circa 1930-1970 (Box 89, Folder 507)
      - Card file of Yale publications received by Yale University Library, Circa 1930-1970 (Box 90, Folder 508)
    - 1972-1973
      - A - Al, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 509)
      - Am - Au, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 510)
      - Ba, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 511)
      - Be - Bi, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 512)
      - Bl - Bre, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 513)
      - Bri - By, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 514)
      - C - Carn, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 515)
      - Carr - Ci, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 516)
      - Cl - Com, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 517)
      - Con - Cu, 1972-1973 (Box 91, Folder 518)
      - D, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 519)
      - E - Fe, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 520)
      - Fi - Fu, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 521)
      - G - Gi, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 522)
      - GI - Gy, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 523)
      - Ha, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 524)
      - He - Hil, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 525)
      - Him - Hy, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 526)
      - I, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 527)
      - J, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 528)
      - K, 1972-1973 (Box 92, Folder 529)
      - La, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 530)
      - Le - Lie, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 531)
      - Lil - Ly, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 532)
      - M - Ma, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 533)
      - Mc - Mi, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 534)
      - Mo - My, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 535)
      - N - Neu, 1972-1973 (Box 93, Folder 536)
      - New - No, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 537)
      - O, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 538)
      - P - Pe, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 539)
      - Pf - Pr, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 540)
      - Pu - Q, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 541)
      - R - Ri, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 542)
      - Ro - Ry, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 543)
      - S - Se, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 544)
      - Sh - Sm, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 545)
      - So, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 546)
      - Sp - Sy, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 547)
      - T, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 548)
      - U - V, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 549)
      - Wa, 1972-1973 (Box 94, Folder 550)
      - We - Win, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 551)
      - Wis - Wit, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 552)
      - Wo - z, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 553)
      - Appraisals, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 554)
      - Library Associates, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 555)
      - Yale, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 556)
      - Gift Statistics and Donors Lists, 1972-1973 (Box 95, Folder 557)
    - 1973-1974
      - A - Ame, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 558)
      - Amh - Az, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 559)
      - Ba, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 560)
      - Be - Bi, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 561)
      - Bl - Bo, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 562)
      - Bra - Bro, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 563)
      - Bru - By, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 564)
      - C - Can, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 565)
      - Car, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 566)
      - Cas - Cha, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 567)
      - Che - Cl, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 568)
      - Co - Cu, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 569)
      - D, 1973-1974 (Box 96, Folder 570)
      - E, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 571)
      - Fa - Fl, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 572)
      - Fe - Fu, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 573)
      - G - Gi, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 574)
      - Gl - Gu, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 575)
      - Ha, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 576)
      - He - Hi, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 577)
      - Ho - Hu, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 578)
      - I, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 579)
      - J, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 580)
      - Ka, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 581)
      - Ke - Ku, 1973-1974 (Box 97, Folder 582)
      - La, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 583)
      - Le - Lil, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 584)
      - Lin - Lit, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 585)
      - Lo - Ly, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 586)
      - M - Ma, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 587)
      - Me - Mi, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 588)
      - Mo - My, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 589)
      - N - Neu, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 590)
      - New - No, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 591)
      - O, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 592)
      - Pa, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 593)
      - Pea, 1973-1974 (Box 98, Folder 594)
      - Pen - Pl, 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 595)
      - Po - Q, 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 596)
      - R, 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 597)
      - S - Se, 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 598)
      - Sh - Sm, 1973-1974 (Box 99, Folder 599)
      - So - Sz, 1973-1974 (Box 100, Folder 600 - 608)
    - 1974-1975
      - A - Am, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 609)
      - An - Az, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 610)
      - Ba, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 611)
      - Be - Bo, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 612)
      - Br - By, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 613)
      - C - Ce, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 614)
      - Ch - Cn, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 615)
      - Col - Conn, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 616)
      - Cons - Cu, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 617)
      - D, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 618)
      - E - Ec, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 619)
      - Ed - Ex, 1974-1975 (Box 101, Folder 620)
      - F, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 621)
      - Ga, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 622)
      - Ge - Gr, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 623)
      - Ha, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 624)
      - He - Hop, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 625)
      - Hor - Hu, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 626)
      - I, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 627)
      - J, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 628)
      - K - Ke, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 629)
      - Kh - Ku, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 630)
      - L - Le, 1974-1975 (Box 102, Folder 631)
      - Li - Ly, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 632)
      - Ma, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 633)
      - Me - Mi, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 634)
      - Mo - My, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 635)
      - N - Nes, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 636)
      - Neu - Nu, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 637)
      - O, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 638)
      - Pa, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 639)
      - Pe, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 640)
      - Pf - Q, 1974-1975 (Box 103, Folder 641)
      - R - Re, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 642)
      - Ri - Ry, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 643)
      - S - Se, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 644)
      - Se - Sl, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 645)
      - Sm - Sp, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 646)
      - St - Sz, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 647)
      - T - Th, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 648)
      - Ti - Ty, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 649)
      - U, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 650)
      - V, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 651)
      - Wa, 1974-1975 (Box 104, Folder 652)
      - We - Wh, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 653)
      - Wi - Wz, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 654)
      - XYZ, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 655)
      - Yale, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 656)
      - Interdepartmental Libraries, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 657)
      - Library Associates, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 658)
      - Appraisals over $1000.00, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 659)
      - Statistics, serial continuations and cancellations, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 660)
      - Statistics and donor list, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 661)
      - Copies of questions on 74-75 donor list, 1974-1975 (Box 105, Folder 662)
    - 1975-1976
      - A - Al, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 663)
      - Am, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 664)
      - An - Aw, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 665)
      - Ba, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 666)
      - Be, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 667)
      - Bl - Bo, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 668)
      - Br, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 669)
      - Bu, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 670)
      - C - Cam, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 671)
      - Can - Car, 1975-1976 (Box 106, Folder 672)
      - Ce - CI, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 673)
      - Cob - Conk, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 674)
      - Conn - Cons, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 675)
      - Coo - Cz, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 676)
      - D - De, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 677)
      - Dh - Dz, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 678)
      - E - Ed, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 679)
      - Ei - Ex, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 680)
      - F - Fi, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 681)
      - Fl - Fu, 1975-1976 (Box 107, Folder 682)
      - G - Gre, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 683)
      - Gh - Go, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 684)
      - Gr - Gy, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 685)
      - H - Hat, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 686)
      - Hau - Hn, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 687)
      - Hod - Hop, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 688)
      - Hor - How, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 689)
      - No folder, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 690)
      - Hu - Hy, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 691)
      - I, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 692)
      - J, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 693)
      - K - Ke, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 694)
      - Ki - Ky, 1975-1976 (Box 108, Folder 695)
      - La, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 696)
      - Le - Lig, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 697)
      - Lil - Ly, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 698)
      - M - Mal, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 699)
      - Man - Mar, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 700)
      - Mas - Me, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 701)
      - Mi, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 702)
      - Mo - My, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 703)
      - Na, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 704)
      - Ned - New H, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 705)
      - New M - Ny, 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 706)
      - O, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 707)
      - Pa, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 708)
      - Pe, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 709)
      - Pf - Po, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 710)
      - Pr - Q, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 711)
      - R - Rh, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 712)
      - Ri - Ry, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 713)
      - S - Se, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 714)
      - Sh - Sm, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 715)
      - So - Sp, 1975-1976 (Box 110, Folder 716)
      - St, 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 717)
      - Su - Sz, 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 718)
      - T - To, 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 719)
      - Tr - Ty, 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 720)
      - U, 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 721)
      - V, 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 722)
      - W - Wa, 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 723)
      - We - Wh, 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 724)
      - Wic - Win, 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 725)
      - Wis - Wy, 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 726)
      - Y - Z, 1975-1976 (Box 111, Folder 727)
      - Yale, 1975-1976 (Box 112, Folder 728)
      - Cancellations, Discards, etc. Serials, 1975-1976 (Box 112, Folder 729)
      - Gift Continuation Project Statistics, 1975-1976 (Box 112, Folder 730)
      - Gift statistics and donor list, 1975-1976 (Box 112, Folder 731)
      - Lib. Assoc., 1975-1976 (Box 112, Folder 732)
      - Transfers, 1975-1976 (Box 112, Folder 733)
      - Appraisals over $1000.00, 1975-1976 (Box 112, Folder 734)
    - 1976-1977
      - A - Am, 1976-1977 (Box 113, Folder 735)
      - An - Az, 1976-1977 (Box 113, Folder 736)
      - B - Be, 1976-1977 (Box 113, Folder 737)
      - Bi - Bra, 1976-1977 (Box 113, Folder 738)
      - Bre - By, 1976-1977 (Box 113, Folder 739)
      - C - Ca, 1976-1977 (Box 113, Folder 740)
      - Ce - Ch, 1976-1977 (Box 113, Folder 741)
      - Ci - Cok, 1976-1977 (Box 113, Folder 742)
      - Col - Con, 1976-1977 (Box 113, Folder 743)
      - Coo - Cy, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 744)
      - D - De, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 745)
      - Di - Dz, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 746)
      - E - El, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 747)
      - Em - Ex, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 748)
      - F - Fl, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 749)
      - Fo - Fu, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 750)
      - G - Gh, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 751)
      - Gi - Gu, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 752)
      - Ha, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 753)
      - He - Hi, 1976-1977 (Box 114, Folder 754)
      - Ho - Hw, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 755)
      - I - Ins, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 756)
      - Int - Iu, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 757)
      - J, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 758)
      - K - Ke, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 759)
      - Ki - Ky, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 760)
      - L - Ler, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 761)
      - Lev, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 762)
      - Lew - Li, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 763)
      - M - Man, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 764)
      - Mar - May, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 765)
      - Me - Mi, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 766)
      - Mo - My, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 767)
      - N - Na, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 768)
      - Ne - NCW H, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 769)
      - New J - Ney, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 770)
      - Ni - Ny, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 771)
      - O, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 772)
      - Pa, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 773)
      - Pe, 1976-1977 (Box 116, Folder 774)
      - Pf, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 775)
      - Ph - Po, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 776)
      - Pr - Q, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 777)
      - R - Rh, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 778)
      - Ri - Ry, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 779)
      - S - Sc, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 780)
      - Se - Si, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 781)
      - Sl - Son, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 782)
      - Sou - Sov, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 783)
      - Sp - Ste, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 784)
      - Sto - Sz, 1976-1977 (Box 117, Folder 785)
      - T, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 786)
      - No folder, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 787)
      - U - V, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 788)
      - W - Wh, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 789)
      - Wi - Wz, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 790)
      - X, Y, Z, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 791)
      - SC Floaters Discarded, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 792)
      - Donor list and statistics, ticklers and memos, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 793)
      - Serials for sale fist, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 794)
      - Yale College Programs of Study - Calendar, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 795)
      - Divinity Library Donor Lists, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 796)
      - Engineering Library Donor Lists, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 797)
      - Medical Library Donor Lists, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 798)
      - Yale, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 799)
      - Library Assoc., 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 800)
      - Transfers, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 801)
      - Appraisals over $1000.00, 1976-1977 (Box 118, Folder 802)
    - 1977-1978 (Box 118, Folder 803)
      - A - Ama, 1977-1978 (Box 119, Folder 804)
      - Ame - Ayt, 1977-1978 (Box 119, Folder 805)
      - Bab - Bev, 1977-1978 (Box 119, Folder 806)
      - Bha - Bo, 1977-1978 (Box 119, Folder 807)
      - Bra - Bril, 1977-1978 (Box 119, Folder 808)
      - Brit - But, 1977-1978 (Box 119, Folder 809)
      - Ca - Cen, 1977-1978 (Box 119, Folder 810)
      - Cep - Clu, 1977-1978 (Box 119, Folder 811)
      - Co - Cz, 1977-1978 (Box 119, Folder 812)
      - Da - De, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 813)
      - Di - Dz, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 814)
      - E - Edi, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 815)
      - Edu - Ev, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 816)
      - F - Foo, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 817)
      - For - Fz, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 818)
      - G - Ge, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 819)
      - Gi - Go, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 820)
      - Gr - Gu, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 821)
      - H - He, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 822)
      - Hi - Hy, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 823)
      - I - Iz, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 824)
      - J - Ju, 1977-1978 (Box 120, Folder 825)
      - K - Ke, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 826)
      - Ki - Ky, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 827)
      - L - La, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 828)
      - Le - Lew, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 829)
      - Li - Ly, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 830)
      - Mc- Mar, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 831)
      - Mas - Mex, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 832)
      - Mic - Mil, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 833)
      - Mo - My, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 834)
      - N - Ne, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 835)
      - Ni - Ny, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 836)
      - O- Ora, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 837)
      - Orc - Ow, 1977-1978 (Box 121, Folder 838)
      - P - Pa, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 839)
      - Pe - Ph, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 840)
      - Pi - Q, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 841)
      - R - Rh, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 842)
      - Ri - Rob, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 843)
      - Roc - Ry, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 844)
      - S - Se, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 845)
      - Sh - Soul, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 846)
      - Sout - Sp, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 847)
      - Sta - Stol, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 848)
      - Ston - Sz, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 849)
      - T - Tj, 1977-1978 (Box 122, Folder 850)
      - To - Tw, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 851)
      - U - V, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 852)
      - W - Wh, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 853)
      - Wia- Win, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 854)
      - Wit - Wy, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 855)
      - X-Y-Z, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 856)
      - Yale, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 857)
      - Yale Library Associates, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 858)
      - Yale Medical Library Associates, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 859)
      - Appraisals over $1000,00, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 860)
      - Transfers, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 861)
      - Kline Science Library, List of donors, 1977-1978 (Box 123, Folder 862)
    - 1978-1979
      - A - Al, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 863)
      - Al - Az, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 864)
      - Baa - Bal, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 865)
      - Bam - Baz, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 866)
      - Bb - Bi, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 867)
      - Bj - Bo, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 868)
      - Bp - Bt, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 869)
      - Bu - Bz, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 870)
      - Ca - CI, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 871)
      - Cm - Cz, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 872)
      - D, 1978-1979 (Box 124, Folder 873)
      - E, 1978-1979 (Box 125, Folder 874)
      - F, 1978-1979 (Box 125, Folder 875)
      - Ga - Ge, 1978-1979 (Box 125, Folder 876)
      - Gf - Gz, 1978-1979 (Box 125, Folder 877)
      - Ha - Hd, 1978-1979 (Box 125, Folder 878)
      - He - Hz, 1978-1979 (Box 125, Folder 879)
      - I, 1978-1979 (Box 125, Folder 880)
      - J, 1978-1979 (Box 125, Folder 881)
      - K, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 882)
      - La - Le, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 883)
      - Lf - Lz, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 884)
      - Ma - Md, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 885)
      - Me - Mz, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 886)
      - N, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 887)
      - O, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 888)
      - P, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 889)
      - O - Ri, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 890)
      - Rj - Rz, 1978-1979 (Box 126, Folder 891)
      - Sa - Se, 1978-1979 (Box 127, Folder 892)
      - Sf - Sz, 1978-1979 (Box 127, Folder 893)
      - T, 1978-1979 (Box 127, Folder 894)
      - U - V, 1978-1979 (Box 127, Folder 895)
      - Wa - We, 1978-1979 (Box 128, Folder 896)
      - Wh - Wz, 1978-1979 (Box 128, Folder 897)
      - X - Y - Z, 1978-1979 (Box 128, Folder 898)
      - (Yale), 1978-1979 (Box 128, Folder 899)
      - Library Associates, 1978-1979 (Box 128, Folder 900)
      - Yale Medical Library Associates, 1978-1979 (Box 128, Folder 901)
      - Misc, Donor lists, 1978-1979 (Box 128, Folder 902)
      - Gift Statistics, 1978-1979 (Box 128, Folder 903)
      - Gift Statistics, 1978-1979 (Box 128, Folder 904)
      - Appraisals over $1000.00, 1978-1979 (Box 128, Folder 905)
      - Acquisitions Statistics, 1978-1979 (Box 129, Folder 906 - 907)
- Records, 1939-1968; Accession 19ND-A-114
  - Acquisitions, gifts and exchanges
    - Correspondence, 1939-1967 (Box 1, Folder 1-7)
    - Correspondence, 1952-1969 (Box 2, Folder 1-4)
- Correspondence, 1950s-1960s; Accession 19ND-A-115
  - Correspondence, 1950s-60s (Box 1)
- Records concerning gifts, 1925-1971; Accession 19ND-A-116 (Box 1–3)
- Records of gifts received, 1976-1977; Accession 19ND-A-117
  - Gifts received records, 1976 July - 1977 June (Box 1)
- Card file records, Circa 1975-1985; Accession 2014-A-004
  Restricted to Office of Origin only
  General
  All boxes are dated circa 1975-1985 unless otherwise noted.
  - Area collections (Box 1)
  - Asia/New Zealand/Africa (Box 2)
  - Europe
    - Austria-Poland (Box 3)
    - Portugal-Yugoslavia (Box 4)
  - Exchange abbreviations (Box 5)
    Box includes miscellaneous files
  - Exchange statistics, 1975-1980 (Box 6)
  - Exchange statistics, 1980-1985 (Box 7)
    Box includes miscellaneous files and files on the publication: YUL Reports of the Library
  - General (Box 8)
  - General (Box 9)
  - General (Box 10)
  - General (Box 11)
  - Gift continuations
    - A-L (Box 12)
    - M-T (Box 13)
    - U-Z (Box 14)
      Box includes vendor contact information files
  - Gift donors
    - A-I (Box 15)
    - J-R (Box 16)
    - S-Z (Box 17)
  - Mailing lists: AJS-YULGZ (Box 18)
  - North and South America (Box 19)
  - Series sent on exchange
    - A-W (Box 20)
    - Yale CL-Yale STU (Box 21)
    - Yale STU (Box 22)
    - Yale STU-Yale WES (Box 23)
    - Yale WES (Box 24)
      Box includes files on the University Bulletin
  - Yale Review/Connecticut Academy (Box 25)